jolicloud.com 2013-05-02

# Jolicloud - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

### Last updated May 22, 2012.

Jolicloud (“we”, “us”, or “our”) is committed to respecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal data. We are not in the business of selling information about you; we use the information you share with us for the sole purpose of running and improving our services.

Any information that you provide to Jolicloud is subject to our Privacy Policy, which governs our collection and use of your information, the options available to you regarding our use of your information, and how you can access and update your information.

By using the Jolicloud site and Jolicloud services, you agree to abide and be bound by this Privacy Policy, which may be modified or updated from time to time. You will always find the latest version of our Privacy Policy here.

### What information is collected or used?

  * #### Login credentials upon sign-up

In order to sign up for Jolicloud, you must provide us with your name and email address and create a username and password. We use this information to ensure that only you will have access to your account.

  * #### Additional profile information

You can add additional information on your profile besides your username and email address, including (but not limited to) your birthday, gender, country where you live, as well as a picture of yourself. Once you have registered, you can visit your profile at any time to add or remove personal information about yourself.

  * #### Third party authentication

When you add a service to Jolicloud, we use a technology called OAuth to authorize Jolicloud to access that account. OAuth is a secure protocol that gives us access to your data without actually giving us your password. You can revoke OAuth access either within Jolicloud or within the third party service.

  * #### Third party data

For each of the services you authorize Jolicloud to access, we create an index of data from that service. This allows us to aggregate and present the data in one place and provide search, filter and organisational functionality for it. Data collected may include photographs, music, videos, links to websites, documents, location information and social network activity. Social network data may include information you have entered on that site including your age, hobbies, comments, ‘likes’, etc.

  * #### Cookies

We send HTTP cookies to your browser or device to keep you logged in. We also use cookies to better understand how users interact with Jolicloud.

  * #### Usage and interaction

We collect information about your usage of and interaction with the Jolicloud websites and Services including computer and connection information, application version, device capability, browser type, language preference, current date and time, bandwidth, statistics on page views, and traffic to and from our websites and services. 

We may also collect data pertaining to your “Friends” and list you as a “Follower” on their profile or collect and share other information for your activity, including (but not limited to) friends you have connected with, upgrades you have made, content you have made public or private, collections you have created, made public or followed, and applications you have installed, removed, created and accessed.

We never link this information to any personally identifiable information such as your email, name, or any other information that could be used to identify you. This data is used in aggregate to improve the quality of our site and to track usage trends.

  * #### Tracking technologies and third party cookies

Our service providers’ use of cookies is not covered by our privacy policy. Jolicloud uses third party tracking services, which use cookies to track non-personally identifiable information (including but not limited to your IP address) about the visitors to our site and services in the aggregate to capture usage and volume statistics. We in turn use these statistics to help us understand how our services are used. We have no access to or control over these third party cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Jolicloud only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party.

  * #### User communications

As part of providing you the Services, we may need to provide you with certain communications (such as service announcements and administrative messages) from time to time. These communications are considered part of the Services and your Jolicloud account, which you may not be able to opt-out from receiving.

When you communicate with us electronically, we keep those communications in order to respond to them and improve the quality of our product and our support. We may from time to time ask for additional information for security reasons or to provide specific services to you.

### How is your information shared?

Jolicloud Me is an index of your personal content from the services which you have connected to your Jolicloud Me.

Private content on Jolicloud Me is visible only to you.

Public content on Jolicloud Me is visible to all of your friends inside Jolicloud Me.

The privacy settings you applied on the services you connected to Jolicloud Me (i.e. Facebook, Twitter, Picasa, Flickr, Tumblr and/or Instagram) are applied to all of the content appearing inside Jolicloud Me. Specifically,

  * Content which is available only to you or which has been restricted to a group on the original service will be private inside Jolicloud Me
  * Content which is available to anyone on the original service will be public by default inside Jolicloud Me.

Your “Public Items” is a stream of your Jolicloud Me items that are public as defined above.

Collections which you create are all public by default. It is possible to change this setting and to make your collections private only to you.

### What is your information used for?

The reason we collect information is to provide you with a reliable, safe, efficient and personalized experience. Jolicloud collects and uses, or has third party service providers acting on Jolicloud’s behalf collecting and using, personal data relating to you, as permitted or necessary to:

  * deliver services for you,
  * provide you with help & support,
  * let you know about service status, updates and faults,
  * compare information for accuracy,
  * get your feedback on our services and on how we are doing,
  * resolve disputes,
  * verify your identity,
  * evolve, enhance and measure the Jolicloud site and Jolicloud services,
  * set up and undertake Jolicloud's marketing or promotional activities and events.

We do not sell your personal data.

We do not disclose your private information except in the limited following situations:

  * when we have your consent to do so, such as when you use a third party service to connect to your Jolicloud account,
  * when we work with trusted third parties partners who carry out specific functions and services for us, we may share your personal information with them. However this is only done to the extent necessary for them to perform the functions and services we require of them, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy,
  * when required to do so by a law regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to tackle fraud, security or technical issues; or to preserve Jolicloud's rights or property.

We may from time to time send you updates about your account or our products and services. You may however opt out of receiving promotional emails at any time. Opting out can be done [here](http://drive.jolicloud.com/settings/notices).

### Information security

We take all reasonable steps to safeguard the security of any information you input or send to us by using secure services and encryption technology, by implementing all necessary security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. However, please understand that no online security measure can be 100% guaranteed.

### Right of access and modification

According to the French data protection law dated 6th January 1978, you have a right to access and modify your personal data stored by Jolicloud. Accordingly, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes.

To access and modify your personal data, please send an email to privacy@jolicloud.com identifying yourself and the information you would like us to access, correct or remove. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

The data we are indexing from your third party services can be deleted at any time. To remove services you no longer want to see in your Jolicloud please go to your settings. We will delete the third party authentication data and the third party data completely from our servers as fast as is technically feasible - this could talk approx 20 minutes. Records of your interaction with Jolicloud may persist in our server and communication logs.

  * #### Transfer of your Information outside the EEA

Your information may be collected, stored, accessed and further processed (by us or data processors acting on our behalf) in the United States and other territories both inside and outside the EEA. If we process your information on servers or using service providers based in such territories, we will ensure that your Information is afforded the same level of protection as in the EEA. You should be aware that privacy laws in the United States may not be equivalent to the laws in your country, and by using the Platform, you consent to the transfer, storage and processing of your personal information in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

  * #### Changes to this Privacy Policy

The Privacy policy is governed by French law. The privacy policy may be modified or updated from time to time. If we make material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on our website prior to the change becoming effective. The most current version will always be on this page.

  * #### Links to Third Party Services 

We do not own or operate the applications available through the Jolicloud Application Directory. We do not collect data relating to your use of such third party services. These third party services may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. Jolicloud shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

  * #### Contacting Jolicloud

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us any time at privacy@jolicloud.com.
